easyrentcars.com 2018-12-18

# Easyrentcar's Privacy Policy |Easyrentcars.com

Our goal is to make [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) the most trusted site in the car rental industry and related tourism industry. We value the trust you have placed in us, and are committed to protecting and safeguarding any personal information you give us. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please email us at [support@easyrentcars.com](mailto:support@easyrentcars.com).  

 **What kind of personal information does[www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) use?**

This site [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) collects personally information ("Personal Information") when you make a rental car booking or request a quote, such as your name, email address, phone number, and so on. To make it easier to manage your bookings, you can open a user account. This allows you to save your personal settings, review previous bookings and manage future bookings.

The personal information we collect is used to provide you with better service and products. Based on the User Login Mechanism, we will open the User Rating And Comment Function in the near future. In addition, under the premise of your permission, we will also be able to forward your information to the website you order travel products to save you time and avoid repeating of information.

We may collect some information about usage habits (tourism-related) of members for better understanding and to provide better service to you. These data will help us to develop functions, information and services to better meet the needs of users. At the same time, the information will be used to display the target ad, but no personal information will be used to send the target ad, and we will not collect any personal information unless otherwise specified.

In addition, we may collect some specific technical information about the machines you are using. The technical information we collect may include: IP address, Operating system version, browser version, monitor resolution, recommended sites and so on, all of which will be used to provide a better user experience and more convenient services.

 **How can you control marketing emails?**

Upon completion of a quote or rental car booking we provide options to opt out of marketing and sales emails, if you have remained opted in, we hope you enjoy receiving our emails, but if you would prefer not to be kept up-to-date with our special offers, you can opt out, or unsubscribe, from marketing communications at any time using the ‘Unsubscribe’ link in each newsletter.

 **How does[www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) share your data with third parties?**

In certain circumstances, we may share your personal data with third parties.

We promise to give special protection to the privacy and security of your personal information. Only authorised personnel are permitted to access personal information in the course of their work

The rental car you booked: In order to complete your booking, we need to transfer relevant booking details to the rental car supplier you have booked with. This may include information such as your name, age, contact details (email, address and telephone number), date and place of birth, passport information, driving licence information, payment information and any preferences you specified when making a booking.

This site [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) will not disclose the visitor's personal information to a third party without the consent of the visitor. This site will not assume any legal responsibility under the following circumstances where:

  1\. We are required by law to share your personal information with government or investigative authorities. Such requirements include court orders, subpoenas and orders arising from legal processes and criminal investigations. 

  2\.  You tell user password to others or share the account with others, which results in disclosure of personal information.

  3\. Any other factors that interrupt normal operation of the network caused by force majeure and results in the personal information being disclosed, lost, stolen or modified, such as computer problems in 2000, hacker attacks, computer viruses invade or attack, or temporary closure due to government control.

  4\. This site [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) is linked with other partner websites around the world but will not be responsible if your personal information is disclosed by these partner websites.

  5\. This site [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) would never disclose your personal information if not for the purpose of protecting you from urgent risks.

  6\. This site [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) will not be responsible for the privacy policies of these business partners.

 **How can you control the personal information you have given to[www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/)?**

This site [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) tries to be open as it can be in terms of giving people access to their personal information. Individuals can request a copy of their information by contacting us in writing at the following email support@easyrentcars.com or at the address below stating 'Subject Access Request' in the subject, we may ask for further information to validate the identity of the requester to ensure the security of the data we hold.

 **What security procedures does[www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) put in place to safeguard your personal information?**

We use appropriate business systems and procedures to protect and safeguard the personal information you give us. We also use security procedures and technical and physical restrictions for accessing and using the personal information on our servers. Only authorised personnel are permitted to access personal information in the course of their work.

 **Cookies and other Browsers**

We use cookies and similar technologies to collect information. Cookies also help us keep your account safe. By continuing to visit or use our services, you are agreeing to the use of cookies and similar technologies for the purposes we describe in this policy.

A cookie is a small file placed onto your device that enables [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/)  features and functionality. For example, cookies enable us to identify your device, secure your access to [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) and our sites generally, and even help us know if someone attempts to access your account from a different device. Cookies also enable you to easily share content on [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) and help us serve relevant ads to you.

Cookies can be used to recognize you when you visit [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/), remember your preferences, and give you a personalized experience that's in line with your settings. Cookies also make your interactions with [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) faster and more secure. Additionally, cookies allow us to bring you advertising both on and off the [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) sites, and bring customized features to you through [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/) plugins such as our "Share" button.

You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. By visiting our Services, you consent to the placement of cookies and beacons in your browser and HTML-based emails in accordance with this Privacy Policy, which incorporates by reference our Cookie Policy.

We use advertising technologies and web beacons to collect information. We give you a number of ways to opt out of targeted ads, including through the Ad Choices icon shown with any ads we serve on third-party sites. If you do not want us to track your behavior on third-party sites, you can opt out. If you do not opt out, you consent to our use of beacons and other advertising technologies.

 **Third-Party Service Suppliers**

We may use third-party service suppliers to process your personal information on our behalf for the purposes specified above. For example, we may use service suppliers to send the booking information on our behalf to the supplier of the rental car you booked with us, or we may instruct third parties to contact you. When a booking requires it, we may also work with third-party payment service suppliers to facilitate payment or payment guarantees. We also work with third-party advertisement networks to market services on other platforms, or involve third-party suppliers for analytical purposes. The third parties involved in any of these services will be bound by confidentiality agreements and will not be allowed to use your personal information for any purposes other than those specified above.

 **About changes to privacy terms**

This Privacy Policy comes into force as of April 25, 2017. The right to modify and update the privacy clauses resides with [www.easyrentcars.com](https://www.easyrentcars.com/). 

Please inform Easyrentcars.com of any breach of this Agreement and any Single Service Terms, and announcements at Easyrentcars.com. 

You, the User, can contact Easyrentcars.com through the following contact information:

 **Easy Tour International Limited**

 **Office Address:  **Rm 19-115, No. 14 Tai koo Wan Road, Quarry Bay, Hong Kong

 **Tel Number:** +852-301-84900
